{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Agile processes is :",
      "answers": [
        "1. never use formal inspection or peer review processes",
        "2.always use formal inspection or peer review processes",
        "3. rarely use formal inspection or peer review processes ",
        "4. all answers is uncorrect"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Many agile methods argue that: ",
      "answers": [
        "1. The customers would always press the developers about the time",
        "2. producing a requirements document is a waste of time",
        "3. better to use incremental requirements engineering and express requirements as ‘user stories’. ",
        "4. Answers 2 and 3 are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "The software requirements document should be:",
      "answers": [
        "1. organized so that system customers can use it",
        "2. organized so that software developers can use it ",
        "3.  organized so that other systems can use it",
        "4. Answers 1 and 2 are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": " system requirements that should describe the system services in detail is a :",
      "answers": [
        "1. Functional",
        "2. Non-Functional",
        "3. Domain",
        "4. all requirements"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": " what Factor affecting the extent of the review?",
      "answers": [
        "1. nothing affecting it.",
        "2. developers",
        "3. society",
        "4. Project magnitude"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
  {
    "question": " In direct Reviews",
    "answers": [
      "1. Identify risks.",
      "2. locate deviadions from conventions",
      "3. product uproval.",
      "4. record Errors"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "4",
    "level": "2",
    "team": "animal"
  },
  {
    "question": "which one is NOT a  objectives type of review?",
    "answers": [
      "1. Finding and fixing code problems ",
      "2. Checking the systematicity of code before entering it into the system ",
      "3. Criticizing the programmer who wrote the code",
      "4. Testing the coding ability of other programmers"
    ],
    "correct_ans": "1",
    "level": "3",
    "team": "animal"
  },
    {
      "question": "Black Box tests is :",
      "answers": [
        "1. Access to unit testing manually or automatically",
        "2.Shadow access to testing at all levels while looking at the system code",
        "3. Access to functional system tests",
        "4.Neither answer is correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": " collecting requirements by:",
      "answers": [
        "1. Questionnaires",
        "2. Observations",
        "3.interviews",
        "4. all answers are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "there is :",
      "answers": [
        "1 Stages of testing",
        "3 Stages of testing",
        "5 Stages of testing",
        "2 Stages of testing"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": ": Which of these is a Types of maintenance",
      "answers": [
        "1. Corrective Maintenance",
        "2.  programmetive Maintenance",
        "3. publicetive Maintenance",
        "4. all answers are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is a Maintenance?",
      "answers": [
        "to make efficient of the Development testing to make the system more effective",
        "it is that with the finish of project we need to to make sure that all the system data is complate and correct ",
        " it's to ensure the continuous and efficient operation of the system ",
        "4. all answers is uncorrect"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Development Testing is  :",
      "answers": [
        "where the system is tested during development to discover bugs and defects",
        "where a separate testing team test a complete version of the system before it is released to users",
        "where users or potential users of a system test the system in their own environment",
        "4. Answers 1 and 2 are correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is an Architectural Patterns? ",
      "answers": [
        "it's the process of determining a software system’s architecture ",
        "it's an approach to software development",
        "it's a part of junit test",
        "it's a set of architectural design decisions that are applicable to a recurring design problem"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "we can document an Architectures by ____?",
      "answers": [
        "conceptual view",
        "logical view",
        "process view",
        "4. All the answers is correct"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"


    }
   ]
}

